# Pozdnyakov Arseniy

GitHub: orson88 Email: malecsenya@gmail.com Telegram: @tkrfrf

## Summary

I am a specialist with 2+ years of vast experience in various Data-connected specialties and DevOps: DWH, Batch Big Data processing, Online/Offline ML services and knowledge in Time-Series, Tabular and Deep Learning tasks. And of course, the underlying infrastructure being Kubernetes, bare-metal.

### Experience

Reksoft Consulting

Moscow, Russia

• MLOps

October 2023 — Present

- ClickHouse microk8s FastAPI MLFlow MiniO Seldon Core Tabular ML Spark Monitoring
  - Took part in creation of a prototype DWH and made two stages dev and test for underlying infrastructure
  - $\circ\,$  Administration and configuration of databases
  - Made prototype architecture for offline/online tabular ML tasks

DigitalMS ♂

Moscow, Russia

• DataOps Hadoop Kafka FastAPI SQL Docker Python February 2023 — October 2023

- Deployment, administration and load testing of software on testing stage.
- Development of REST APIs for internal usage
- ETL/ELT development and administration with AirFlow

FEMC ophthalmology clinic ♂

Moscow, Russia

• Data Engineer (project)

November 2022 — January 2023

PostgreSQL Python AirFlow PowerBI BI Visiology DWH Docker

• Made a small-scale DWH from scratch, with NiFi/MiniO/AirFlow/Postgres/Clickhouse with Dashboards on PowerBI

Analytics Center

Moscow, Russia

Junior Data Scientist

Tabular ML Python Time Series SQL nifi

November 2021 — August 2022

- Batch/Offline Time-Series prediction (Econometrics models) of consumer goods. Mainly food in supermarkets at countryscale.
- Made an interpretable simple regression model for predicting medical supply limits during COVID outbreaks
- Made simple ETLs of data for reports and analysts

#### Skills

Languages:

Python, SQL, Bash, Go(syntax)

Libraries & Frameworks:

FastAPI, DVC, ClearML/MLflow, sqlalchemy, airflow, sklearn, pytorch, plotly/seaborn, streamlit

pandas, numpy

Instruments:

Docker | Linux | Git | Kafka | HDFS | Hive | microk8s | Gitlab CI | Airflow | MLFlow | PySpark

Seldon Core | ClickHouse | GreenPlum | (S3) | AirFlow

#### Education

Master, 2022-2024:

Machine Learning and HighLoad Faculty of computer science,

Higher Schools of Economics

Bachelor, 2018-2022: Applied maths and IT,

Faculty of IT and big data analysis,

Financial University